

OLEG KUTS

Frontend developer









ABOUT

Junior Web Developer with 1+ years of experience in Web development. Strong experience in development of web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript. Moderate knowledge and experience with React, jQuery. Good hands-on experience with Ps, Figma, GIT.

CONTACT INFO

City: Kyiv

Telephone: +380667338900

Email: oleg.kouts@gmail.com

LinkedIn: @oleg-kuts

Portfolio: oleg-kuts-portfolio.netlify.com

GIT: github.com/oleoot



SKILLS

Html/Css JavaScript React jQuery Node.js Sass Ps/Figma

WORK EXPERIENCE

Interviewer

GFK Ukraine | June 2016 - August 2016

Conducted social interviews and interviewed many people on various topics.

Consultant

Goodwine | June 2017 - June 2019

Consulted people about fruits and vegetables, displayed goods, worked with databases.



EDUCATION & TRAINING

Web Development Courses at IT Education Academy

HTML/CSS October 2018 - December 2018

Designed and developed frontend applications, using web technologies such as HTML5, CSS3.

JS Base December 2018 - January 2019

Understood how JavaScript works, completed tasks including working with data types, arrays, loops mastered working with DOM.

JS Advanced January 2019 - February 2019

Used acquired knowledge to build more complex projects using objects, prototypes, animations, and implementing ES6 to it.

LANGUAGES



PERSONAL QUALITIES

Purposeful

Tend to solve the problem, no matter how difficult it is.

Open

Take criticism well and always ready to help another person.

Full of energy

Active, I do not waste time, but do my job great.

Sociable

Like meeting new people, because I believe that from them I can get new knowledge and experience.